Why?
What's going on?
The entire culture of moe is gone from Akiba?
Okarin, wait up!
Okarin!
What's wrong?
Where's the Toranoana? The Animate?
The Mandarake? The Gamers?
What are you talking about, Okarin?
Why would those be in Akiba?
That's why I'm going to Nakano to get my comics.
Mayuri,
you work part-time at MayQueen, right?
MayQueen?
MayQueen NyanNyan!
Impossible...
Faris was the one who requested to bring the culture of moe to Akiba.
She sent a D-Mail preventing that from ever happening?
With just one message,
the whole town changed.
Even the billions of heartbeats in the world
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
are nothing to you but insignificant
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Whether we’re trapped in the past or lamenting over the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
predetermination does not allow even the slightest mistake
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The infinite dreams and futures before us
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are but vain privileges allowed to us
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finitude is what both clock hands show
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
toward a cruel destiny and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
So now I cross worldlines every second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
because I want to protect that smile of yours
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And so, a time loop without sadness will once again
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
engulf me, the lone observer
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
It's hard to believe that MayQueen used to be here.
MayQueen? Is that a potato?
During summer, I prefer noodles to potatoes.
It isn't a potato...
If MayQueen never existed, then how did we meet Faris?
Well, it's thanks to potato ramen that we met her.
What do you mean?
You don't remember?
On the day of the Rai-Net Tournament in Ikebukuro,
I got sick from the potato ramen I had for lunch,
so I withdrew.
And then?
Mayushii and you entered as a pair,
and you went up against Faris.
You totally lost,
but Mayushii and Faris became friends.
I see.
Look, look, Luka.
I bought this cosplayer's photobook yesterday in Nakano!
So cute...
The past changed, but our relationships haven't?
You seem to have lots of time
on your hands with this Bon Festival, lab mem girls.
Hello there.
Look! Cute, huh?
Hey! It's Sedona from Blood Tune!
It's really detailed!
There's a swimsuit version too.
I wish I could be like that.
I don't have those proportions.
It's okay!
Flat is justice!
I know!
Why not take all the lab mems and go to the beach?
With Kurisu too!
Everyone, wear your school swimsuits, okay?
I'm not going swimming with a pervert.
Um, well... I mean, if it's just the girls,
I'd love to!
Why not be honest, Christina?
You don't want
anyone to see the mole on your rear,
so you can't go. Right?
There's no mole!
And if it's just the girls,
then Lukako can't go.
Huh? Why not?
I told you earlier, right?
That Lukako's actually a guy.
You're a real jerk, you know?
How can you call a girl a guy?
Mayushii doesn't like it when you say stuff like that.
Isn't that really mean?
Wait!
Why are you crying?
Apologize to Urushibara. Now.
No, seriously.
Why would I apologize? It's true—
It's fine!
So that's what you think of me, Okabe.
No, no, no, Lukako! You're really...
How long will you keep that up?
I'm going home!
Wait!
You're a guy!
Look! Right here, you have...
It's gone! There's nothing here!
Okabe, stop it...
Lukako, you're a girl?
I've been saying that this whole time!
Yo! Uh, what's wrong?
Don't worry about it.
Just a bit of torture...
Torture?
By Makise Kurisu?
Yes, but I've rectified the misunderstanding...
I think...
She got your legs?
Don't touch my legs!
She made me sit on my knees for an hour!
No! I mean, I was tortured.
Oh... That isn't torture.
You almost sound like you've been tortured.
Well, I am a warrior.
It's a perfect day for biking...
Yeah?
Hey...
Want to go for a ride?
Is this what you call biking?
I came to Tokyo to find my father.
To find him?
Did he disappear or something?
I haven't seen him in years.
I can't even remember his face.
But I know he's in this city.
This is my only clue...
a badge he used to own.
Then you shouldn't waste time at a part-time job, should you?
There's some stuff going on, you know?
But there's one chance.
My dad might show up tomorrow at a certain place.
If I miss that chance, I'll have to leave this town.
There's somewhere I have to go.
I'm a busy person, you know?
Well, I always planned to give up if I couldn't meet him.
You're worried, aren't you?
I can understand that feeling.
But that's too bad!
Your luck ran out the minute
you spoke to the great mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma.
You are now Lab Mem 008!
You will be our guinea pig.
Wh-What are you going to do?
Change the past.
You may think me cruel if you like,
but there's no escape for you.
Send a D-Mail to your father before he leaves.
Tell him not to leave his daughter behind.
You're a good person, you know that?
What?
Somehow, I feel a bit better now.
I have to get back.
Thanks for talking to me!
Listen!
Whether you see him tomorrow or not,
come by the lab!
I will use your sentimentality
for an experiment with the D-Mail!
You really are a mad scientist!
That's terrible...
I will now explain
the parameters of Operation Eldhrímnir.
More Norse myths?
If the part-time warrior meets her father,
we'll hold a celebration,
a last supper in Tokyo, for her.
And if she doesn't,
we'll try to cheer her up,
and then send a D-Mail.
Where's Daru?
He's meeting his online friends tonight,
so he said he can't join us.
The fool!
But I've taken steps.
To: Daru
Now is the time to choose
Faris's cooking or your meeting.
Which will you choose?
I sent this message.
Faris's cooking or your meeting.
Which will you choose?
But Faris can't come, right?
Faris has never met the part-time warrior,
so it's pointless for her,
but Daru has a duty to participate in this operation.
Um... I've never met this Suzuha person either.
That's fine.
I'm sending you all shopping for the banquet.
And you?
I will follow the part-time warrior
and report in on the situation.
Don't you dare.
Let the father and daughter have their time together.
That's right.
Come shopping with us!
I'm following—
I said no!
Don't tell me what to do, assistant...
Do you want to sit on your knees again?
This time for three hours...
Now then! Let's get things ready for the party!
I'm watching you.
What's wrong, Okarin?
Nothing.
This is...?
I think sweet curry will be nice.
Or maybe spicy?
What do you think?
U-Uh... Spicy, I guess.
Oh, yeah! Suzu's a part-time warrior, right?
If she's a warrior, she'll want spicy.
Um... Next is the meat, the meat!
Beef sure is expensive...
Hey, Okarin.
You don't look good.
Back there, you would've normally said...
"The Organization's interference has increased the price of beef!
Has Operation Time Sale begun?" or something.
But you need to use Norse mythology there, not "Time Sale."
It's me.
The Organization's interference has caused unexpected expenses
in Operation Audhumbla.
I'm requesting additional funds for the operation.
The first star!
Venus?
Hey, Okarin?
Remember in elementary school
when you got really sick with a high fever?
Yeah, and the world was panicking over Y2K.
Mayushii was really scared you would die then.
So, I prayed to the sky.
And then, there was a shooting star.
I said to the shooting star,
"Don't die, Okarin!" three times.
And the next day, you got better!
And so, I saved your life.
No, that's not true.
It was the choice of Steins Gate
that I survived back then.
Was it?
It was.
I see.
Hey, remember what you said
when you got sick and collapsed?
"Everything I saw began to flow together,
and suddenly, I began to shake and couldn't stand up."
You looked just like that
in Faris's condominium.
The feeling I had when I got that fever
was just like the feeling I get when I move worldlines.
Which means...
I attained my magic eye, Reading Steiner,
at that moment?
We're back!
Welcome back.
Do you smell something weird?
I think it's the smell of Kurisu's apple pie.
What?
This?
Want Mayushii to help too?
Can you boil an egg?
Sure!
Um... Can I use the PhoneWave?
N-No!
If you microwave a raw egg, it'll explode!
I'll make the egg.
Then you chop up the mushrooms, Mayuri.
Okay!
W-Wait!
You don't need mushrooms or boiled eggs for apple pie!
It's for the salad to go with it.
I don't think a boiled egg and mushroom salad really go with apple pie.
And you,
stop chopping up mushrooms over there!
Move!
It's me.
It seems I've released the seals that bound a dark god.
If I don't contact you within the hour,
tell my parents I loved them.
Okabe, do you have a rice cooker?
Where's Faris?
Hashida, you've been deceived.
Faris said she couldn't come.
Seriously?
Hey, Okarin!
Next time I get a chance, I'll take care of it.
Screw you!
I was really looking forward to my time machine forum meeting.
Time machine forum?
It's with a sci-fi message board I frequent a lot.
A professional author was supposed to go too!
This is an interestingly shaped mess kit.
Don't touch it.
That's not a mess kit.
It's Future Gadget #4, Moad Snake.
A claymore?!
It's made to look like one.
It's a super-instant humidifier.
Oh, this?
S-Stop! Don't!
I'm sorry, Okabe.
Don't worry about it.
Next time, don't touch it.
Hey, couldn't we use this?
A vacuum cleaner?
Nope!
It's Future Gadget #3.
Or #2?
#5!
And its name is
"Once Again I Have Created Something Worthless"
by Goemon.
We made it so you can use a vacuum cleaner's output to warm a dryer.
Give it to me.
Wait!
When you use that, you need to turn off
any other appliances, or...
...it'll trigger the breaker.
Where's the flashlight?
Is this it?
No, Miss Luka.
That's a radish.
U-Um, where's the breaker?
If you walk around...
I told you...
Ow...
The breaker's in the front hall.
Are you okay?
What's so funny?
I'm sorry.
But...
the lab I worked at in America had some of
the best people from around the world.
But they all had really huge egos,
so it was also a really hostile place.
Compared to them, your lab is really childish,
but it's a fun place to be.
I-I'm not praising you, okay?
I was just kinda thinking that...
I guess maybe I simply wanted friends.
I, um...
I think of you as a companion.
You told me before, didn't you?
That I was your dear companion.
That made me really happy, I guess.
Do you have a fever?
N-No!
What? I'm trying to rethink my opinion of you...
Stupid Okabe!
Suzu's late.
I wonder if she met her dad.
I bet they're finally spending time together.
I told her to come to the lab either way.
But it's late.
We're aborting the operation.
You guys, go on home.
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
Damn her!
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
From:
Part-Time Warrior
Subject: I'm sorry
Goodbye
Does she plan to leave the city by herself?
I, Hououin Kyouma, will not allow that!
Damn it!
Where did she go?
That's right...
If I send a D-Mail telling myself to follow her
no matter what this afternoon...
But...
is it okay for me to use D-Mail
to change the past any more?
You're a good person, you know that?
Somehow, I feel a bit better now.
I am the great mad scientist, Hououin Kyouma!
What do I have to fear?
Do not give in to your assistant's threats.
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
Follow Suzuha!
Do not give in to your
assistant's threats. Follow Suzuha!
Yo.
Good morning, Part-Time Warrior.
Slacking off?
Last night, we were all up really late.
I'm so tired.
Last night,
we had a last supper for you,
so you could be our guinea pig.
Right?
But the experiment never happened.
I don't know my dad's phone number.
I want to confirm something.
How did I catch you?
Were you drinking?
You're underage. You shouldn't do that.
Just answer me.
Well, I was heading back from the time machine forum meeting...
Time machine forum?
That's where your dad was supposed to show up?
Yeah, my dad's calling himself Titor.
John Titor?!
Not John... Barrel.
Barrel Titor.
I told you that yesterday.
Didn't you take a video of it on your phone?
Last night was so fun...
It would've been more fun without Makise Kurisu, though.
Her apple pie was absolutely horrible.
But Urushibara Luka's curry was great!
Your lab's kinda nice, you know?
Everyone's friends, and you always seem to have fun.
I've never felt like I fit in so much anywhere else in my life.
Then you're welcome anytime.
Come whenever you like.
You're a lab mem now.
Yeah.
I'll try to search for my father a little more!
kisei sareta shikai mujihi naru
With my field of view restricted
juuni no shihai nogarerarenai
I cannot escape the merciless control of the twelve
ansoku no asu wo negatta
While wishing for a tomorrow of repose
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
I headed for the sacred event horizon in my hand
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
Pledges are imprisoned, and false evidences are showing their outline
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
This world of life blindly lets the time pass by
habatake butterfly
Spread your wings
kiseki no butterfly
butterfly of miracles
anata he sasagu
I dedicate it to you
namida no butterfly
Oh butterfly of tears
mabushii butterfly
butterfly of radiance
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
everything will now be rewritten